export const androidInterviewQA = [
    {
        question: "What is Android?",
        answer:
          "Android is an open-source operating system based on Linux, primarily used for mobile devices such as smartphones, tablets, and smart TVs.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is an Activity in Android?",
        answer:
          "An Activity represents a single screen with a user interface. It is one of the core components of Android applications.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the Android Manifest file?",
        answer:
          "AndroidManifest.xml provides essential information about the app to the Android system, including app components, permissions, and minimum SDK version.",
      },
      {
        question: "Difference between Activity and Fragment?",
        answer:
          "An Activity is a complete screen, while a Fragment represents a portion of UI inside an Activity and is reusable across multiple activities.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is Intent?",
        answer:
          "Intent is a messaging object used to request an action from another app component, such as starting an activity or service.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is ViewModel?",
        answer:
          "ViewModel is part of Android Architecture Components that stores and manages UI-related data in a lifecycle-conscious way.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is LiveData?",
        answer:
          "LiveData is an observable data holder class that respects the lifecycle of app components like Activities and Fragments.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is RecyclerView?",
        answer:
          "RecyclerView is a flexible and efficient view for displaying large sets of data by recycling views to improve performance.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is ANR?",
        answer:
          "ANR (Application Not Responding) occurs when the UI thread is blocked for too long, causing the system to show an error dialog.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is Jetpack Compose?",
        answer:
          "Jetpack Compose is Androidâ€™s modern UI toolkit that uses declarative programming to build native UI with less code.",
      },
  ];
  